翻譯&校對：william2568
遠鑒字幕組製作
[Visionary] 0day-sub
我們在美麗的西班牙伊比沙島
Here we are in beautiful Ibiza, Spain.
美麗的沙灘
Beautiful sand.
美妙的海浪
Beautiful waves.
穿著我最喜歡的那條短褲
My favorite shorts.
還有我最愛的女人 她馬上就要成為...
And my favorite girl who is about to get...
我的天
Oh, my God!
嘿
Hey!
- 把那給我 - 別鬧了
- Come on, give it to me. - No! Stop! Come on!
- 米奇 - 這拍的挺好嘛
- Mitch! - This is great!
我是認真的
I'm serious.
我的天 你真可愛
Oh. Oh, my God. That is so cute.
親愛的
Honey, this is like...
讓我拍一會嘛
Let me film for just a couple minutes.
- 我們就像在度蜜月一樣 - 我的天
- It's like we're honeymooners. - Oh, my God!
度蜜月呢
♪ Honeymooners ♪
- 度蜜月?
"Honeymoon"?
- 對啊
Yeah.
我們還沒結婚呢
We're not married.
卡特麗娜·哈珀
Katrina Harper...
你是我最好的朋友
You're my best friend in the whole world.
親愛的 不要
Oh, my God. Babe, stop it. You're gonna make me...
如果你哭了 對我來說簡直就像世界末日一般
If you get emotional, you're gonna kill me.
我盡量忍著
I'm trying to get through this, babe.
我愛你 你在我心裏最重要
I love you, more than anything.
你願意嫁給我麼
Will you marry me?
我的天
Oh, my God!
我願意
- Yes! - Yeah?
我願意 米奇·拉普
Yes, Mitch Rapp.
我願意嫁給你
I'll marry you.
抱歉 用一隻手不太方便
Sorry, it's hard one-handed.
喜歡麼 這是我媽媽的戒指
You like it? It was my mom's ring.
我喜歡它
I love it.
我喜歡你
I love you.
- 你還在錄像麼 我的天 - 是的
- I'm still... - Are you filming? Oh, my God!
是的 我在錄像 我要把這些都錄下來
Yeah, I'm still recording. I'm trying to get this.
不要嘛 米奇
Come on, Mitch!
就像把你這個樣子錄下來 現在懂了嘛
This is why I was filming now. You see, now you get it.
笑一個
Smile.
我去拿點喝的
I'm gonna get drinks.
- 好麼 - 好
- Okay. - Yeah?
- 別去太久
Don't be too long.
- 不會的
I won't, I won't.
- 我愛你
I love you.
- 我也愛你
我會回來的
I'll be back.
我們在水裏訂婚了 喝點東西慶祝一下
Engagement drinks in the water, people.
謝謝
Oh. Thank you. Thank you.
很棒 親愛的 有人給我們鼓掌
Very sweet, thanks. Babe, we're getting applause.
我愛你
I love you.
謝謝
Thank you.
你好
Hola. Como estas?
需要什麼嘛
What can I get you?
能不能給我來兩杯
Um, can I just get two drinks, please?
兩杯 嗯...
Dos bebidas, if that's right...
我剛剛訂了婚 需要點特別的東西
Um, I just got engaged, so something special.
隨便喝點什麼就行
It can be anything, though.
你真幸運 夥計 祝賀你
Oh, you lucky guy.
要烈一點的 行麼
Oh, can they be kinda strong too? Is that cool?
謝了 夥計
Thank you, man.
不用這麼烈吧
Oh, whoa. Maybe not that strong.
卡特麗娜！
Katrina!
Katrina?
卡特麗娜！
Katrina!
米奇
Mitch!
卡特麗娜！
Katrina!
兄弟 今晚怎麼樣了
How are you tonight my brother?
準備去度假
I am ready to go on vacation.
點擊加密鏈接下載
Click encrypted link, then download file.
把你們全部炸上天
We're gonna fucking set your shit on fire, man!
去死吧 你們這幫混蛋
Fuckin' burn, motherfucker, burn!
致全世界的兄弟們
To our brothers across the globe...
來加入我們 對抗美帝國主義吧
Come join our fight against American imperialism.
讓他們為 我們的親人 我們的朋友
They will pay for the murder of our families,
我們的孩子之死 付出代價
our friends, and all children.
等著
Hold it, hold it, hold it.
兄弟 你現在心裏是怎麼想的
What is in your heart brother?
我想讓我的雙手沾滿異教徒的鮮血
I want to bathe my hands in the blood of the infidels.
你的按鍵已經被記錄了 快點回復
We are logging your keystrokes. Answer quickly.
誰在悲傷之年去世了
Who was taken in the Year of Sorrow?
哈吉扎 和 阿布塔裏卜
Khadijah and Abu Talib.
在登霄之行中 誰和先知在一起
Who was with the Prophet for the Isra and Mi'raj?
大天使加百列
The Angel Gabriel.
停下 住手
All right, stop! Come on, man!
放開他 放開他
Let him go, let him go. Let him go, let him go!
放開他
Break it up. Let him go!
老兄 你腦子有問題吧
What the fuck is your deal, man?
快點 拉普 滾出去
That's it. You're done, Rapp. Get out.
他老是這樣
He keeps doing this shit.
滾出去
Get out!
真是他媽美好的一天
Have a nice fucking day.
你他媽真是個瘋子
You were out of line.
繼續訓練 快點
Back to work. Keep moving.
快回來
Get outta there!
你會把自己害死的 你個蠢貨
You're gonna get yourself killed, you dumbass!
拉普 還要我再跟你說一遍麼
Rapp, why I gotta tell you again?
抱歉 納茲爾先生 我沒注意到已經過10點了
Sorry, Mr. Nazir. I didn't realize it was past 10:00.
我盡量控制噪聲
I'll try to keep it down.
別再做運動了
Yeah, enough with the sports.
明白了 謝謝您 納茲爾先生
Copy that. All right. Thanks, Mr. Nazir.
海灘恐襲案嫌犯 阿德南·曼蘇爾
他又上線了
He's up again.
你收到一條新信息 查看信息
你會來到這裏麼
Will you come here?
無論安拉在何處召喚我 我都能前往參戰
Allah wills that I join the struggle wherever I am called.
的黎波里 利比亞
願主的平安在你上!
要是我的話 我就不會選你了
If it were up to me, I would not have chosen you.
但他們可不這麼認為了
But others have decided differently.
安拉指引著我們前進
Whomsoever Allah guides there is none to misguide.
先知妹妹的名字叫什麼 願她安息
What is the name of the sister of the Prophet, peace be upon him.
胡扎法·賓特·哈里斯
Huzafa bint Al-Haarith.
你錯了
Wrong.
那不是他的妹妹
She was not the Prophet's sister.
她被尊為先知的妹妹
She is honored as the sister of the Prophet, peace be upon him...
因為他們都吮吸過先知母親的乳汁
...because both suckled from her blood mother, Halimah al-Sa'diyah.
你為什麼來這
Why have you come?
幫助 阿德南·曼蘇爾完成他的使命
To help Adnan al-Mansur achieve his people's destiny.
如果真主願意的話
Inshallah.
我要你看著我的眼睛說
I wanted to look in your eyes.
我不信任你
I don't trust you.
我已經準備好成為殉道者了
I'm prepared to die a martyr.
我要怎麼樣才能贏得你的信任
What can I do to earn your trust?
不
No!
快讓開
Step away, now!
別打了
Come on!
放開我
The fuck off me!
他已經死了 結束了
He's dead, it's over.
冷靜 冷靜
Easy. Easy. Take it easy.
本區域安全
Area's secure.
你想殺了他們 過去把他們都殺了
You wanted to kill them all, and then go on killing.
是不是挺極端的
Pretty extreme, don't you think?
我覺得一點也不極端
No, I don't think that's extreme at all.
他們這樣的人
I think people like that deserve to die
就得讓他們死的很難看
in the worst ways you can imagine.
關於你父母的死 你還記得多少
What do you remember about your parents' death?
那是一場車禍
Car crash.
我當時在馬薩諸塞州
I was in Massachusetts.
他們在突尼斯
They were in Tunisia at the time.
當時14歲
I was 14.
我只記得這些
That's what I remember.
你的行為舉止方面有些問題
You started having discipline problems.
曾被三個寄宿學校退學
Got yourself kicked out of three boarding schools.
我知道 只是不知道為什麼會這樣
Yeah, yeah. I know. I wonder what that was about.
談談那個沙灘上發生的事
Let's talk about what happened after that day on the beach.
我的天 又談這個 你在逗我麼?
Oh, Jesus Christ. Again? Are you kidding me?
是的 又談這個
Yeah, again.
你在那之後是不是就自暴自棄了
You gave up everything after that, didn't you?
你本科在布朗大學就讀
Your grad studies at Brown University.
我失去了興趣
I must have lost interest.
對一切都失去了興趣?
In everything?
不 不是這樣
No, not everything.
再見 費雷恩博士
See you later, Dr. Frain.
明天 同一時間見面麼
See you tomorrow, same time?
換個新面孔來見你
I like the new look.
我是艾琳·肯尼迪
Irene Kennedy, CIA Deputy Director
中情局反恐部副主任
in charge of Counterterrorism.
我知道你是誰
I know who you are.
你知道你在這呆了多久麼
Any idea how long you been here?
30天
30 days.
夠你想通一些事了
Enough time for you to figure out a couple things.
是啊 關於我自己的事 我想通了不少
Yeah, yeah. I've figured out a lot about myself.
過的很充實 謝謝
It's been a very reflective time. Thank you.
當時在現場你可能撐不過20秒
You wouldn't have made it through the next 20 seconds there alive.
天知道呢
I guess we'll never know now, will we?
你告訴費雷恩博士 說你要殺掉曼蘇爾
You told Dr. Frain you thought you were gonna kill Mansur
掃平他的老巢
and wipe out his whole cell.
這只是個開始
For starters.
米奇 你心裏還打著更大的算盤吧
You had an even bigger agenda, didn't you, Mitch?
你是怎麼想的
What did you think,
你想一個又一個掃平恐怖分子的據點?
you were gonna jump from cell to cell taking out terrorists?
鏟奸除惡?
Righting the world's wrongs?
我這不是搞定了曼蘇爾麼
Got to Mansur, didn't I?
比你有能耐啊
I mean, it's more than you accomplished.
我要跟你說一些事
I'm gonna let you in on something.
我們這的人不知道要拿你怎麼辦
Our people here, they don't know what to do with you.
很多人就覺得把你扔進一個高級別監獄就行了
A lot of them think we should just throw you in a supermax.
至於我嘛
Me?
米奇 我對你的計劃很感興趣
I like your agenda, Mitch.
如果你加入我們 我可以幫你實現你的目標
I can help you with it, if you throw in with us.
我們甚至可以把你培養成專業的特工
We can teach you how to play with the big boys.
讓我先打斷你一下
Yeah, let me stop you right there.
您認為我18個月前沒考慮過
You don't think I considered that 18 months ago?
加入中情局麼
Joining the CIA?
我覺得自己一個人行動幹掉曼蘇爾
I made the decision to pursue Mansur on my own
是因為我覺得我自己能辦到
'cause I knew I could get it done.
你要明白 只有我才能幫你
What you need to understand is that I'm the only way.
達成你的目的
To get what you want.
為什麼我要相信你
Why the hell would I trust you?
因為我相信你
Because I believe in you.
你只能指望我了
And I'm all you've got.
已確認
What's been confirmed is
一個退役的俄國
the enriched plutonium has been stolen
核設施裏的濃縮鈾遭竊
from a decommissioned Russian nuclear facility.
如果他們找到一個核起爆器
If they get their hands on a nuclear trigger
再找一個能造核彈的物理學家
and a physicist to build it,
他們就能裝備核武器 引爆核彈
they'd be able to arm it and detonate it at any time.
湯姆?
Tom?
他的測試結果十分優秀
He's testing through the roof.
我從沒見過這麼厲害的
Might be the best I've ever seen.
我們監控了他6個月
We've had him under surveillance for six months.
關注了他的格鬥術 槍法
Martial arts, gun skills.
我以前監控過不少這種民間人員
I've surveilled dozens of these vigilantes.
他很與眾不同
This one is different.
艾琳 這些情況我都清楚
Yeah, well, I've gone over these, Irene.
他不服從命令 難以控制
He's noncompliant, he's oppositional.
我們跟著他找到了曼蘇爾的老巢
He got us into Mansur's cell.
比我們強太多了
That's a hell of a lot more than we ever managed.
獵戶星是我們這的
All right, Orion is an elite unit, Irene.
秘密精英特種部隊
A secret unit.
只向你我二人報告
Reports to you, me, and no one else.
我不想為這人
I don't want to be responsible
可能鬧出的亂子負責
for that kind of mistake.
你說話的語氣和赫爾利一樣啊
Now, that's Hurley talking.
他給我打了兩次電話 就談這個
Yeah, well, he's called me twice about this.
這樣的人能把他嚇壞
This kind of psych profile scares the hell out of him.
他估計會覺得
As far as he's concerned,
你給他派了個一心想復仇的瘋子
you're sending him a Section 8 with an ax to grind.
在沙灘上發生的事
What happened to that kid on the beach,
改變了他的一生
it changed him.
就算通過訓練 你也不可能對任何人起那麼大的影響
You can't train that into someone.
他現在的心理狀況正是我夢寐以求的
His psych profile is exactly what I've been looking for.
做過測謊儀測試麼
Polygraph?
完美通過
Flying colors.
那就祝赫爾利好運吧
All right. Good luck with Hurley.
艾琳
Oh, Irene.
我們兩個小時內會收到
We'll have fresh intel on the Russian
關於俄羅斯濃縮鈾事件的情報
plutonium situation in two hours.
保持電話聯繫
Stay by your phone.
羅阿諾克峽谷 弗吉尼亞
你可以把眼罩摘下來了
You can take the blindfold off.
- 關於這傢伙 有什麼我要知道的?
So, what do I need to know about this guy?
- 你是說斯坦·赫爾利麼
Stan Hurley.
他是個勇士
He's a warrior.
前海豹突擊隊特種兵
Ex-Navy SEAL.
我父親和他一起在波斯灣服役過
My daddy served with him in the Persian Gulf.
你負責這個項目麼
Did you go through this program?
我只是瞭解情況 不負責這個計劃
I went through a program. Not this one.
這個計劃不只是培養一個間諜
It's not like becoming a spy or Special Ops,
或者特工那麼簡單
none of those things.
知道了
Good.
米奇·拉普的心理報告
米奇 你的目標是什麼
So, what are your goals, Mitch?
我的目標?
My goals?
我的目標就是如果他們知道我要來了
My goal is to have them lie awake at night,
會嚇得睡不著覺
knowing I'm coming for them.
你不抽煙了?
I thought you were supposed to be on the patch.
- 你看了他的測試結果麼
You saw those tests.
- 看了
Yeah, I saw them.
十分優秀
He's off the charts.
優秀的人我也見過
I've seen off the charts before.
軍隊出身的人員可能會養成一些難以擺脫陋習
And he's got none of the bad habits
然而他就不必了
he'd have to unlearn if he had military training.
難以擺脫?
Unlearn?
斯坦
Come on, Stan.
讓你手下的那些海豹突擊隊進大城市裏試試
You drop one of your Navy SEALs in an urban setting,
周圍的人能輕鬆發現他們是當兵的
you can spot the boot camp on them a mile away.
- 現在不是..
We're not fighting the...
- 不是冷戰那時候了 我知道
Cold War? Yeah, I know.
副主任女士 你一直在提醒我這點
You keep telling me that, Miss Deputy Director.
我的天 你這麼尊敬我了
Oh, wow. "Miss Deputy Director."
你父親會支持我這麼做的
Your daddy would agree with me.
我每48小時聯繫你一次
I'll be checking in with you every 48 hours.
我早上坐飛機去倫敦
I'm on a plane to London in the morning.
趕緊去抽幾根吧
And go back on the patch, for God's sake.
別讓我失望
Don't prove me wrong.
她不會回來了
She ain't coming back.
嘿
Hey.
看著我
Eyes front and center.
抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉? 你以為我是你的大學教授麼
"Sorry"? Do I look like one of your college professors?
小子 你要稱呼我為"長官"
You talk to me, you call me "sir," son.
是 長官
Yes, sir.
你他媽的來這幹什麼呢
What the fuck you doing here?
是不是
Did you have some bad things happen to you,
有一些不幸的事發生在你身上
some shitty things happen to you?
你想把那些恐怖分子趕盡殺絕
Now you wanna kill those mean old terrorists.
就是那些你口中所謂的「壞人」
Go get some bad guys.
你憑什麼認為
What makes you think you can make it
你能通過我的選拔?
through my selection process?
- 我能說話麼 長官
Permission to speak, sir?
- 說吧 有話直說
Sure, go ahead if you got something to say.
因為你來這 就是個錯誤
Like this is all a big mistake and you wanna go home.
你想回家麼
You wanna go home? Good.
趕緊滾吧 要不然我幫你滾
Get the fuck out of here. I'll drive you myself.
不想 長官
Not at all, sir.
我覺得我們還是直入主題吧
I was gonna suggest we maybe speed this whole thing up?
我們倆過幾招
My guess is, if you and I go hand-to-hand,
我能否通過
you could probably figure out inside of 20 seconds
你的選拔
whether or not I have what it takes to make it
一看便知
through your selection process.
您覺得呢
So, what do you think?
給你一張床 一個儲物櫃
We got an empty cot, empty footlocker.
看你夠不夠格留在這裏了
They're both yours as long as you can last.
我覺得可以
Sounds good.
跟我來
Follow me.
待會見
See you out there.
順便說一句 我聽說了不少關於你的事
Heard a lot about you, by the way.
想看看你有多大的能耐
Excited to see what you got.
來殺我
Kill me.
總有人以為這樣就能要我的命
People think you can slice a man's throat like this.
只有拍電影才可能這麼容易
That's only in the movies.
就是這
Right there.
用力壓下去
Do it.
不會有動靜 不會搞成亂攤子
No noise. No mess.
維克多 你來
Victor, you're up.
我操
What the fuck, man?
誰他媽帶了把刀
Who grabs a fucking blade?
上啊
Come on, you fuckin' pussy. Let's go!
應該注意到後面的情況
You gotta have eyes in the back of your head.
你猶豫一下 就死了
You flinch, you die.
獵戶座計劃的核心就是完成任務
Orion is about the mission.
能者就上
It ain't about you.
你要是戰死沙場 你就是個孤魂野鬼
You go down out there, you're a ghost, you don't exist.
沒有人會回來救你的
There's nobody, nobody coming back for you.
要是你被俘了
You're about to be captured.
那就告別這個世界吧
Bye-bye.
伊朗大使館 倫敦
我們現在瞭解到
We now know 15 kilos of plutonium-239
俄羅斯那邊有15千克的鈽-239不翼而飛
went missing during the Russian breach.
足夠造一個核武器了
It's enough to build a full-scale nuclear weapon.
但可能需要傾全國之力才能完成核武器的建造
But that would likely require the resources of a nation-state.
作為伊朗參謀總長
As Iranian Chief of General Staff,
我們對此事同樣關切
I share your concern.
我們同你們一樣 都在關注事態發展
We have been monitoring the situation as you have.
我們也不知道是什麼情況
I'm afraid we too are in the dark.
對伊朗來說 建造核武器
For Iran, of course,
是不可能的
a nuclear weapon is off the table.
我們簽訂了條約的
We have a treaty.
有一些伊朗人對這個條約不太滿意
You have countrymen who are not too happy about that.
我們監控了你們的濃縮項目
We monitor your nuclear enrichment program pretty closely,
發現有人在俄羅斯黑市上購買了這些鈽-239
but black market plutonium-239 from Russia...
關於黑市的情況 高層無從得知
Would be difficult for inspectors to detect.
您是肯尼迪女士 對吧?
Ms. Kennedy, yes?
作為伊朗國防部長 我向您保證
I assure you as Minister of Defense
我們知道如果我們伊朗
that we in Iran recognize how much the spirit of comity
通過任何途徑購買鈽燃料
between our nations would be compromised
都會影響到我們的國家利益
if we were to acquire
有違國際精神
weapons-grade plutonium from any source.
的確如此
Yes, it would.
這話對伊朗境外的勢力同樣適用
Same goes for your clients outside Iran,
真主黨 哈馬斯
Hezbollah. Hamas.
胡塞武裝
The Houthis.
無論在誰的手中 核武器都是危險的
Nuclear weapons are a danger in any hands, Director.
這不就是你們入侵
Wasn't that your pretext for your invasion
我們鄰國的理由麼
of our neighbor to the west?
50萬伊拉克人喪生
One that cost 500,000 Iraqi lives
留下一片廢墟
and left a wake of destruction
整個地區至今動盪不安
from which our region has never recovered.
羅斯塔米將軍 我們是掌握了確鑿的情況才來這會面的
General Rostami, we came only to tell you what we know.
你們這算是威脅我們麼
Is that a threat?
當然不是 比赫茲部長
Of course not, Minister Behruz.
各位先生 感謝參加這次會面
Gentlemen, I very much appreciate you meeting with us.
客氣了
Not at all.
- 很遺憾 不能給你們提供更多情報
I only wish we could offer more insight.
- 謝謝您的支持
Thank you.
我不相信那個羅斯塔米將軍
I don't trust General Rostami.
我們要低調行事
We need to keep this quiet.
獵戶座計劃進行的怎麼樣了
How ready is Orion?
我去問問赫爾利
I'll check in with Hurley.
為什麼好幾個小時了都沒人來
Why is there no one on watch?
你們死定了
You're all dead.
是啊 是啊 知道了
Yeah, yeah. I got it, I got it.
你死了
You're dead.
你想說什麼 快說啊
You wanna say something to me? Say it. Go on, say it.
給你們30秒收拾
You got 30 seconds!
這些是你們的目標
These are your targets.
記住他們
Memorize them.
你們要能辨認出他們來
It's your responsibility to be able to identify them.
殺掉一個武裝人員 得一分
You shoot a combatant, you get a point.
沒擊中的話 會受到一次電擊
You miss, you get a shock.
非戰鬥人員 會受到更強的電擊
You shoot a noncombatant, you get a bigger shock.
如果武裝人員擊中了你
Combatant shoots you...
我就這麼說吧 你那時候會感覺到的
Let's just say you're gonna feel it.
準備好了嗎
Ready?
開始
Go.
赫爾利在幹什麼
What's Hurley doing?
他腦子出問題了
He's fucking with his head.
操
Fuck!
這狗屁的模擬訓練
Fucking AR bullshit.
華沙 波蘭
我們開始吧
Shall we?
好
Okay.
挺不錯的
That's clever.
鈽原料
Raw plutonium.
之前商量好的 是濃縮的
Highly enriched, as promised.
希望如此
Let's hope.
先生們 聽到儀器發出響聲真是太棒了
Wow, that's a beautiful sound, gentlemen.
那我就拿走了
May I?
嗯
Okay.
快轉賬
Wire the money.
馬上就轉
That, I can do.
我就拿手機
This is a cell phone.
把你的車開走 有一個重要官員要經過這裏
Gotta move all the vans. The Cardinal's visiting.
好的
Okay.
五分鐘內就走
Okay. Five minutes.
車裏的是什麼
What's going on in there?
紀念品
Souvenirs.
可能是緊急情況 請求增援
Possible code red, backup needed.
別緊張 沒什麼情況
There's nothing going on.
進來看看嘛
Come in.
目前看來
It now appears that all seven victims
7名死者
were shot with a single weapon,
死於同一把手槍下
believed to be a Glock 29.
車內發現了武器級鈽的蹤跡
Traces of weaponized plutonium
同時還發現了
were detected inside the van
三具俄羅斯人
where the bodies of three Russians
和兩具波蘭警察的屍體
and two Warsaw police officers were found.
俄羅斯政府已經確認
The Russian government has confirmed
核燃料的化學指紋表明
that the chemical footprint of the plutonium in question
這正是托博爾斯克
is a match to the plutonium that was stolen
廢棄核設施內
from the decommissioned
失竊的鈽燃料
processing facility in Tobolsk.
波蘭警方正在和國際刑警組織合作
Security footage is being analyzed by Polish police,
分析監控錄像
now working in conjunction with Interpol,
試圖確認槍手的身份
to identify the shooter and his connection
調查他與鈽燃料失竊案之間有何聯繫
to the missing plutonium.
槍手的身份尚不得知
The identity of the shooter remains unknown...
你好 打擾一下
Hi, excuse me.
有什麼我能幫你的
- How can I help you? - Question.
目標 活動中
- 需要我幫你麼
May I help you?
- 不 謝謝
No, thanks. I'm okay.
嘿
- Ow! Ow! Ow! - Hey! Hey! Hey!
拉普 媽的
Rapp! God damn it!
你要控制住自己
You have to stay under control.
媽的
Dickhead!
這傢伙不知道什麼時候住手
Asshole doesn't know when to quit.
你在逗我麼 我剛剛救了你
You're kidding me, right? I just saved your ass.
拉普 你要知道什麼時候該停手
You've gotta know when the mission's been accomplished, Rapp.
- 長官 這傢伙.. - 聽著
- Sir, he's a fucking... - Which he did.
別以為你只有眼前這一個目標
Never assume your target is the only target.
敵人可能看起來沒什麼威脅 但實際上心狠手辣
The enemy dresses like a deer and he kills like a lion.
我們也要像他們一樣心狠手辣
And that's what we gotta do.
希望你能表現更出色
We just gotta do it better.
那就這樣吧
All right.
你這混蛋
You're an asshole.
出事了
We got a problem.
六周前 有人闖入
Six weeks ago, there was a breach
俄羅斯的一個廢棄鈽燃料設施
at a decommissioned Russian plutonium facility.
我聽說了
I'm aware.
但是你不知道 有15千克的鈽燃料失竊了
What you don't know is 15 kilos of plutonium went missing.
還是武器級的
Weapons-grade.
這麼多
That's a shit-ton of plutonium.
就這麼落入他人之手
And it just changed hands.
我想給你看點東西
I wanna show you something.
看看這個
Take a look at this.
你應該認識這張臉吧
Does that face bong a gong for you?
還是只有我一個覺得這人很熟悉
Or is it just me?
不可能是他
It can't be him.
在轟炸了巴馬科的大使館之後 我們派出無人機又確認了一次
Our drones took him out after the embassy bombing at Bamako.
我們無法完全確定屍體身份
We never got a positive ID.
那是我們這的叛逃特工
That's our mad dog out there.
那行 我們先假設是他
All right. Let's say it's him.
艾琳 不用假設 就是他
It's him, Irene.
現在有一個一石二鳥的機會
This gives us a chance to kill two birds with one stone.
哈姆迪·沙裏夫
Hamdi Sharif.
他是一個武器販子 目前在土耳其
He's an arms dealer working out of Turkey.
四周前他買了一個俄羅斯設計的核裝置起爆器
Four days ago, he purchased a Russian-designed nuclear trigger.
他肯定打算把這玩意轉手
And he's gonna be selling it.
沙裏夫手上有誘餌
Sharif's got the honey.
我們只需等待獵物上鉤
Now we just wait for the bee.
我們派人破壞他們的交易
We go in, we fuck up their deal.
把他們都幹掉
And we take 'em both out.
你去伊斯坦布爾
You're going to Istanbul.
我們那邊有特工接應
We have an agent in place.
她會在機場接你
She'll meet you at the airport.
明白
All right.
安妮卡·奧格登
Annika Ogden. We've had her on the ground over there
她在那潛伏5年了
for five years.
讓拉普參與這次行動
I want Rapp on the team.
你沒開玩笑吧
Really?
斯坦 他已經準備好了吧
He's ready, Stan.
艾琳 我覺得他目前還沒準備好
Actually, Irene, he's not ready.
但我會讓他準備好的
But he will be.
長官 找我有事麼
You wanted to see me, sir?
對 把門關上
Yeah. Shut the door.
我們有任務了
We're shipping out.
把東西放桌上
Set those down there.
你喜歡看電影麼
You like movies?
喜歡
Sure.
我想給你看點東西
I got something for you.
這他媽是什麼鬼
What the fuck is this?
- 我也覺得挺操蛋呢
Yeah, I thought so.
- 你說什麼
You thought so?
- 是啊
Yeah.
你為什麼大難不死呢 拉普
Why are you even alive, Rapp?
你有沒有問過自己這個問題
You ever asked yourself that?
為什麼是你 而不是這些人
Why you? You know, of all those people?
我覺得 肯定是因為你很特別
You're special, I guess.
我的天
Oh, my God!
需要我調高音量麼
You want me to turn it up?
- 我願意嫁給你 - 拿著吧
- I'll marry you! - Take it!
你這混蛋 把視頻關上
You're a fucking coward, you know that? Turn that shit off.
這是我媽媽的戒指 你覺得怎麼樣
What do you think? It's my mom's ring.
關掉
You gonna turn it off?
卡特麗娜!
Katrina!
我是不是應該為你感到遺憾
Am I supposed to feel sorry for you?
我覺得還是不吧
I don't.
你犯了大錯
You made a big mistake.
你讓情緒影響到了你的判斷力
You let emotion cloud your judgment.
永遠不要受制於自己的情緒
Never, ever let it get personal.
明白了麼
You understand?
我明白了
Yeah, I got it.
準備好 早上5點出發
Be ready to go by 5:00.
我們4點半見面
See you at 4:30.
伊斯坦布爾 土耳其
You know what you're gonna do here?
我知道我們來這幹什麼嗎
No, sir.
- 不知道 長官 - 嗯
Correct. You don't.
多觀察 少說話
So keep your eyes open and your mouth shut.
聽我命令
And wait for my orders.
哈姆迪·沙裏夫 房地產大亨 武器販子
Hamdi Sharif, a real-estate mogul/arms dealer.
養活了不少恐怖分子
He's like Santa Claus for terrorists.
一個人渣
Scumbag.
小子 省省你那些
Spare me your junior-year-abroad
幼稚的看法吧
moral opinion, would you, Rapp?
長官 這不只是我的個人看法而已 他就是個人渣
Not really an opinion, sir. Sharif's a piece of shit.
我們這不是聖戰
It's not a crusade.
任務以實用為重 不要受制於...
This mission is practical. Don't make it...
個人情緒?
Personal?
沒錯
Exactly.
明白 長官
Yes, sir.
維克多 你跟我一起
Victor, you're with me.
拉普和安妮卡 你們注意觀察情況
Rapp, you and Annika are eyes on.
沙裏夫日常生活很規律
Sharif has a routine.
看看他最近有什麼異常
Let's see if anything breaks his pattern.
- 明白了麼 - 是 長官
- Got it? - Yes, sir.
我們有48小時完成任務
All right, we got 48 hours.
要做的乾淨利索 不留痕跡
Quick, clean. No footprint.
這裏的各股勢力也是錯綜複雜的
This town's ready to blow as it is.
你要去哪
Where the hell are you going?
抱歉
Excuse me.
解密進行中
- 這他媽太冒進了
That was fucking reckless, Rapp.
- 長官 我這是主動出擊
I took the initiative, sir.
- 可能會搞砸的 - 但我完成了
- He could've been made. - Well, I wasn't.
結果出來了
Here we go.
明天上午11點
11:00 a.m. tomorrow.
同他的情婦見面之前
A meeting at a restaurant on Akbiyik Street.
他會去阿克比克街的餐館
That's right before Sharif goes to see his mistress.
這不符合他平時的日程
That breaks his pattern.
更關鍵的是
I'll tell you what'll break his pattern.
當他的助理告訴他手機丟了
When that fucking assistant tells his boss
那就糟糕了
he lost his goddamn phone.
他不會說的
He won't.
他太怕沙裏夫了 不敢告訴沙裏夫自己搞砸了
He's too afraid of Sharif to let him know he screwed up.
那行 我們明天行動
All right. We go tomorrow.
任務目標是?
What's the mission, sir?
幹掉買家 幹掉賣家
Eliminate the target. Eliminate the recipient.
帶走貨物
Obtain the package.
- 貨物是什麼
And what's the package?
- 到時候就知道了
We'll know it when we see it.
你打頭陣
You're lead.
你做後援
You're backup.
我們在街對面監視現場情況
We will watch from across the street.
我們倆扮演一對情侶
We get to play lovers.
你們倆相戀多久了
How long have you been married?
他以為我們已經結婚了
He thinks we're married.
別想太多
Don't think too much.
你會緊張過頭的
You'll lose your nerve.
我覺得不會
No, I don't think so.
這是你第一次參加任務麼
It'll be your first time.
在我的腦海中 我已經參加了很多次任務了
Yeah, not in my mind.
老大 目標來了
Lead, your friend's arriving now.
收到
Copy.
真他媽的是軍隊級別的保護啊
And he brought a shitload of military protection.
我來搞定他們
I'll take care of the MPs.
親愛的 別發火嘛
Oh, come on, now, honey. Don't be mad.
不不不
No, no, no.
我還有點事 真的
I had a few. Yeah, I did.
我回家後會給你補上的
I'll make it up to you when I get home.
你懂的
You know that.
貝勒貝伊宮附近發現汽車炸彈
Car bombing, near Beylerbeyi Palace.
把這條消息匯報上去 要不然我就割破你的喉嚨
Call it in. Call it in, or I'll cut your fucking throat.
開始行動
Lead, you're a go.
二號 進入指定位置
Survey 2, get in place.
- 小心點 - 我知道的
- Be careful in there. - I got it.
抱歉
Pardon.
起爆器在轎車裏
The nuclear trigger is in the sedan.
目標逃走了
Target's gone. Target's gone.
快走
Get back!
情況如何
Lead?
已死亡
Dead.
任務結束
Mission terminated.
撤到安全地點 已確認
Exfil to secure location. Confirm.
二號 快點他媽的確認執行命令
Survey 2, you better let me hear you fucking confirm.
媽的 亂成一團了 我們撤
God damn it, this is a fucking mess. We're out of here.
老實點
Drive! Drive!
跟著你們的老大
Follow your boss!
別殺我 我是他的助手
Please, I'm just the assistant!
別殺我
Don't hurt me!
快開車
Drive! Drive!
他住這的五樓
He's there right now on the fifth floor.
他做的事我也不喜歡
Please I don't approve of what Sharif does.
別殺我
Don't kill me.
別擔心 我不會殺你的
Don't worry, I'm not gonna hurt you.
我的目標是你的老闆
I'm gonna hurt your boss.
起爆器現在在美國人手上
The American mercenary has the nuclear trigger.
我搞定了我的任務 你搞定你的
I've done my job. It's your problem now.
媽的
Shit.
動作快點
Hurry up!
快滾開
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on.
求求你
No, please.
別殺我
Please, don't. Don't.
求求你
No.
中情局安全屋 羅馬尼亞
你違背了我的命令
You disobeyed a direct order.
不 我決定追蹤目標
No, I made a decision to pursue the target,
完成任務
and I completed the mission.
我來這就是為了完成任務
And, sir, isn't that what I'm here to do? Isn't that my job?
我他媽的要你幹什麼 你就幹什麼
Your fucking job is to do what I fucking tell you to do!
那就是說 你更傾向於讓我離開那
What, you prefer I leave him alive, then,
放那人渣一馬咯
let him go? That piece of shit?
斯坦
Stan?
太好了 你來了 我想給你看點東西
Good, you're here. I wanna show you something.
在那等著
Wait here.
你看 這麼下去
Look at that. That's the kind of bullshit
這傢伙會搞砸的
that could shut us down.
這小子不會遵守命令
Kid can't even follow a fucking order.
維克托沒辦到的事 拉普辦到了
Victor got made. Rapp didn't.
他媽的 你為什麼這麼看好這個小子
Why does this kid give you such a fucking hard-on?
別他媽的跟我這麼說話 我是你的上級
Don't talk to me like that! I'm your superior.
我的上級? 艾琳
My superior, Irene?
正是你的上級 媽的
Your superior, God damn it.
你知不知道 我花了多久才找到
Do you have any idea how long I spent looking
這麼有才 這麼有膽識的小伙子
for someone with that kid's talent and balls?
- 讓拉普留下
Rapp stays.
- 這是命令麼
You're giving me an order?
沒錯
That's an affirmative.
讓我跟他單獨談會
Can you give us a minute?
看看這個
Look at this.
起爆器肯定在那輛車上
The trigger must have been in that car.
看看
Look at him.
就是他
Lookin' at me.
這傢伙幹出來的好事
Everything he did there,
都是我教出來的
I taught him how to do it.
斯坦
Stan.
我真不應該把他從海軍裏招過來
I should've left him in the Navy.
- 我要親手殺了他
I'm gonna kill that son of a bitch.
- 斯坦 聽我說
Stan, listen to me.
重要的是
The only thing that matters now
這個瘋子已經拿到了
is that fucking lunatic has everything he needs
制取核武器的全部環節
to build a nuclear weapon.
他拿到了起爆器 現在要買通一個物理學家
He's got a trigger. Now he needs to buy a physicist.
你現在要搞清楚
We just have to figure out
他們要在哪造核武器
where they're gonna build this thing.
本
Ben.
拉普從沙裏夫家拿到的那台筆記本電腦
That computer our boy Rapp lifted from Sharif's house,
顯示 有一筆兩百萬美元的款項
there's evidence of a $2 million transfer to a bank account in Rome.
打到了一家羅馬銀行的賬戶上 等待支取
Cash prepped for withdrawal.
那我們去羅馬
Rome.
考維爾建築工地 羅馬市附近
這是你的錢
Your money.
部長 我最近讀了一些東西
I've been reading up, Minister.
你們伊朗人可能從小時候起就知道了
You Iranians probably all learn this growing up,
簽訂禁核條約前心裏就有數了
or at least you did before you signed that treaty.
我沒想到還有這麼些有趣的情況
But me, I had no idea about these fun facts.
要是你的話我就不會進去
Yeah, I wouldn't do that if I were you.
起爆點三英里半徑內的人都會蒸發掉
Inside three miles, apparently you just vaporize.
有一些倖免於難
Some folks don't.
他們的皮膚會被烤黑 燒焦
They get all black and charred,
扭曲成一團 沒人知道為什麼會成這個樣子
and dense as lead, and no one knows why.
五英里半徑內 熱浪席捲一切
Inside five miles, everything is sucked into a void,
溫度比太陽中心還高
hotter than the core of the sun.
你們覺得怎麼樣
How about that?
剩下的錢在哪
Where's the rest?
搞定了這個再給你們剩下的錢
You'll get the rest of your money when the job's done.
我派來的物理學家呢
Where is my physicist?
他拿到錢後 我們把他接過來
He'll pick up his money, then we'll pick him up.
他住在羅馬的一家酒店
He's staying at a hotel in Rome.
我們會在一天內完成武器的組裝
We'll need an extra day to configure the weapon, then it's all yours.
你們想殺掉多少猶太人就殺多少
Kill as many Jews as you want.
為我們的勝利祈禱吧 兄弟
Do you practice Salah, brother?
我收到款項 完成任務
I receive my payment, complete the project.
我就是幹這個的 兄弟
That's my practice, brother.
很好
Very well.
納沃納廣場 羅馬
核科學家監控名單
伊斯坦布爾的
Who was that guy?
那傢伙是誰
In Istanbul.
他似乎總是先我們一步
It seemed like he was a step ahead of us.
嘿 你打不打算告訴我
Hey, you gonna fill me in here or what?
有些壞人作惡
There's some bad people planning on doing some bad things,
我們要阻止他們
and it's our job to stop them.
關於維克多 你好像沒說什麼
You still haven't said anything about Victor.
維克多消失了 維克多不存在了
Victor's gone. Victor doesn't exist.
拉普 你覺得我們在這裏是幹什麼的
What is it you think we do here, Rapp?
我們幹掉那些該死的傢伙
I think we kill people who need to be killed.
- 那誰來告訴你應該幹掉誰呢
And who do you trust to tell you?
- 遵守命令就行了
I follow orders.
你想執行命令的時候 才執行命令
No, you follow orders when they suit you.
你加入我們
This whole thing is pretty much
只是實現自己目標的一種手段
just a means to an end for you, isn't it?
長官 我經歷了很多事
A lot's happened in my life, sir.
- 是麼
Really? Huh.
- 是啊
Yeah.
所以你覺得 我們派你到這來
So you think you were sent here
是為了給你人生中的遺憾 憤怒
as an outlet for your self-pity,
愧疚 找個發洩口?
and your anger, and all your guilt. Right?
愛國主義之所以還存在
Patriotism exists
是因為有你我這樣的人為崇高的事業而奮鬥
because people like you and people like me need a higher cause.
為了比我們倆更重要的目標而奮鬥
Something bigger than us.
你腦子裏你認為是"復仇"的玩意
That stink coming outta you
就是狗屁
you like to call "revenge," the rest of us call "shit."
如果你沉浸於其中
And as soon as it starts to feel good,
你就不再是一位合格的特工
that's when you stop being a professional.
那時候的你一文不值
And then what are you?
來說點好消息吧
Tell us something good, darling.
我們入侵了他們的系統
We're in their system.
一有人把錢從沙裏夫的賬上取走
The moment that transfer from Sharif's account is picked up,
我們就能馬上收到消息
we'll know it.
你的笑容像紅海一樣美
Boy, you just smile, and the Red Sea parts.
地中海也很美啊
Works in the Med, too.
你太美艷了
I'll bet it does.
有人把沙裏夫賬戶裏的錢取出來了 兩百萬美元
Cash withdrawal from Sharif's account. $2 million, U.S.
掃瞄中
未找到匹配項
已匹配
發現那個物理學家了 我們走
There's our physicist. Let's go.
歡迎來到博斯科洛大酒店 祝您入住愉快
Welcome to the Boscolo and enjoy your stay.
謝謝
- Thank you very much. - Thank you.
他住1448間
He's in 1448.
我們住他隔壁
And we're next door.
- 密碼
Code in.
- 維克多-查理 1109.
Victor-Charlie 1109.
已確認
Confirmed.
目標住1448房 我們住隔壁
Suite 1448. We're in 1449, right next door.
抓住那個物理學家 把他帶出來
All right. We'll grab the physicist,
我去接應你們
and we'll take out whosever coming for him.
每15分鐘給我打一次信號
Signal every 15 minutes.
嘿
Hey.
我聽說了你的遭遇
I know what happened to you.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我很能理解你
I understand you.
比你認為的更甚
More than you know.
我知道失去我們所愛的人是多麼的心痛
I know what it's like to lose people you love.
我們要把這些壞蛋繩之以法
We're gonna get these fuckers.
我靠
Fuck!
你們他媽的在哪呢
Where the hell are you?
赫爾利
Hurley... Where is he?
在哪裏
I don't know what you're talking...
我不知道你在說什麼
Where is he?
他在哪
He outside?
在外面
Please, no.
饒命啊
Please.
赫爾利 什麼鬼
Hurley, what the fuck?
你不是在盯梢麼 怎麼沒發現他們
I thought you were eyes on, why didn't you spot 'em?
他們比我們早到賓館
They were already in the damn hotel.
當地的黑手黨在與他們合作
Local mafia's working with 'em.
我會聯繫肯尼迪副主任 已經抓到物理學家了
I'll tell Kennedy we have the physicist.
剛才那邊是什麼情況
What the hell just happened out there, huh?
那傢伙把我們的行動搞砸了兩次
That's twice now this guy's blown up our entire op.
目標是什麼
What's the target? Huh? What's the target?
- 我不知道 先生 - 說啊
- I don't know, mister. - Yeah, you do.
你以為我看不出來麼
Do you think I'm stupid?
他是個美國人 他認識你
He's an American. He said your name.
是你訓練了他？
Did you train this guy?
- 你喜歡抽煙麼
You like to smoke?
- 我的天
Oh, Jesus Christ!
你抽煙麼
- Are you a smoker? - I don't...
這習慣可不太妙啊
- Wait! - Bad habit.
慢著 我說我說
Wait, stop! Wait, wait! I know something.
- 什麼 - 我說我說
- What do you know? - I know something.
他們稱那個傢伙為「幽靈」
There is a man... There is a man they call Ghost.
「幽靈」 那個伊朗人就是這麼稱呼他的
Ghost. I think it was an Iranian man said it.
他們在哪造炸彈
- Uh-huh. Where are they building the bomb? - I just...
- 他們在哪造炸彈 - 我只是拿了錢而已
- Where are they building it? - Took the money.
他們在哪造炸彈
Where are they building it?
再給你點時間好好想想
All right, here. Take some time to think about it.
就是那個「幽靈」麼
Ghost. Is that his name?
為什麼他要追蹤你
Why is this guy after you?
是不是出於個人原因?
Something personal, sir?
他們在造核彈
They're building a nuke.
去納沃納賓館
Hotel Navona.
洗個澡吧
- Clean yourself up. - Wait.
別走啊
Don't go.
美國總統命令美國海軍第六艦隊
America's president has ordered the Sixth Fleet
離開意大利那不勒斯的海軍基地
out of the U.S. Naval base in Naples, Italy.
朝西南方向航行
The Sixth Fleet is now southwest off the coast...
我來幫你
Let me help you.
沒事的 我自己來
No, it's okay. I'm fine.
還是我來吧
You're not.
你今天覺得如何
How are you holding up?
我今天很害怕
I was afraid today.
還以為我們都要丟命了
I thought we were going to die.
我要麼一直很害怕 要麼永遠不害怕
Yeah, I'm either always afraid or never afraid.
我不知道我究竟是什麼感受
I don't know which.
貼好了
There you go.
放鬆一會兒吧
Just relax now.
明天再去找「幽靈」
We'll search for Ghost tomorrow.
- 你嚇到我了
You scared me.
- 你是誰
Who are you?
你什麼意思
What do you mean?
你之前說「幽靈」
You said "Ghost."
- 那又怎麼了
What about him?
- 我從來沒提過這個名字
I never told you that name.
赫爾利告訴過我的
Hurley did.
你就扯淡吧
Yeah, I think you're full of shit.
你到底是誰
- Mitch. - Who are you?
- 你有毛病吧 - 你為誰效勞
- Mitch, what's wrong with you? - Who do you work for?
我是中情局的
I'm CIA.
別他媽的騙我
Now don't fucking lie to me!
我沒撒謊
I'm not lying!
你是伊朗人
You're Iranian, aren't you?
放開我
Get the fuck away from me!
你跟那幫伊朗人是一夥的?
Are you working with the Iranians?
說實話
Tell me the truth. Tell me the truth!
去死吧
Go to hell!
你是伊朗情報部門的麼
You Iranian intelligence?
Are you Iranian intelligence?
關於幽靈 你知道多少
What do you know about Ghost?
我們需要解密裝置
We're gonna need the decryption device.
你說的對 米奇
You were right, Mitch.
很難讓這個伊朗間諜開口
This Iranian mole is a tough nut to crack.
我只從她那問到了她的接頭人 阿扎德·阿沙尼
All I could get from her was her handler. Azad Ashani.
他是我的一個朋友
Happens to be a friend of mine.
我要去見見他
I'm gonna go pay him a visit.
- 我跟你一起去
Okay, I'm going with you.
- 不行
No.
我要你待在這
I need you to stay here.
肯尼迪帶了一群中情局
Kennedy's on her way with the CIA team
和摩薩德特工過來
and a Mossad team.
她肯定會問我你去哪了
She's gonna ask me where you went.
我要怎麼說
What the hell am I supposed to say?
沒錯 自己動點腦子
That's right, she is. And you're gonna be smart,
別說出去
and you're gonna keep your mouth shut,
掩蓋我的行蹤
and you're gonna cover my ass.
我還留著它呢
I still have it.
很不錯啊
Very nice.
斯坦 見到你 我總是很高興
I am always happy to meet you, Stan...
但是你每次找我談的事 都讓我高興不起來
But never happy why.
下次我們見面的時候 可以去吃個比薩
Well, maybe next time we'll meet for pizza.
那個女孩子挺有骨氣的
Your girl's tough, by the way.
對她好點
Go easy on her.
她是我的侄女
She's my niece.
嗯
Yeah.
你有什麼消息要告訴我麼
What have you got for me?
這件事的幕後黑手是羅斯塔米將軍
The men behind all this are General Rostami,
伊朗參謀總長
our military chief of staff,
還有國防部長比赫茲
and our defense minister, Behruz.
兩個人都很有權勢
Both are very powerful,
都對禁核協議的簽署心懷不滿
and both are very angry about the nuclear treaty we made with you.
過去的兩年內他們
They have been trying to acquire
一直試圖搞到核材料
nuclear materials for the past two years.
他們找來了那個
And they are the ones
叫「幽靈」的僱傭兵
who hired the mercenary called Ghost.
羅斯塔米在德黑蘭 比赫茲在羅馬
Rostami is now in Tehran, but Behruz is here in Rome.
我讓手下通過他的手機定位到他的位置
Annika has been tracking his movements through his cell phone.
他們在哪造核彈?
And they're building it here?
要是我知道就好了
I wish I knew.
我們抓住他們的物理學家了
We have their physicist.
他們沒法做了
They can't build it without him.
但是
But...
那個僱傭兵
The mercenary asked Behruz
叫比赫茲找一個伊朗的科學家來
to use one of ours, an Iranian.
比赫茲同意了 他們匆忙行事
Behruz agreed. That was rash.
說明他們急於盡快完工
It means they are in a hurry.
他們的目標是以色列?
And the target's Israel?
我也想告訴你更多信息
I wish I had better information for you.
赫爾利在哪
Where the hell is Hurley?
告訴我現在是什麼情況
You gotta tell me what's going on here. Now.
那傢伙是赫爾利培養出來的麼
That guy he trained, who the hell is he?
現在你不需要知道這個
That's not something you need to know right now.
你們在掩蓋什麼
What are you covering up?
當你有了足夠等級的安全許可
When you've got a level-5 security clearance
有了20年的工作經驗 再來找我談這個問題吧
and 20 years' experience, talk to me.
要不然就閉嘴 乖乖幹活吧
Until then, shut up and do your job.
我要你們解密並掃瞄她的手機
I want her cell phone decrypted and scanned.
當地警方一小時前在港口發現一具屍體
Local PD pulled a body from the harbor an hour ago.
胸部中彈
Gunshot to the chest.
死者是 伊朗情報官員 阿扎德·阿沙尼
Iranian intelligence officer, Azad Ashani.
我的天
Christ!
赫爾利就是去見他了
That's the guy Hurley went to meet.
這個混蛋
Stupid son of a bitch!
我覺得我們要去找到赫爾利的下落
All right, so what do we do? We gotta go after him.
他們在造一個他們的核彈 拉普
There's a fucking nuke in play, Rapp.
找到核彈是我們的任務 唯一的任務
That's the mission, and the only mission.
不管你怎麼看
This is now a joint CIA-Mossad operation,
現在這是中情局和摩薩德的聯合行動
whether we like it or not.
給我撥通局長的電話
Can you get the Director on the phone?
你就打算把他棄之於不顧了?
So you're just gonna write him off then?
這就是你的計劃?
That's the plan?
斯坦·赫爾利幾乎算得上是我的親人了
Stan Hurley is the closest thing to family I've got.
要是他現在在場
And if he were standing here right now,
他只會問一個問題
his only question would be,
為什麼我們要浪費時間去討論他的問題
why are we wasting our breath talking about him?
沒你的事了
You're through here.
你準備回程 這是命令
You're going home, that's an order.
現在給我坐下 閉嘴
Now, sit down and shut up.
為什麼你要幫我
Why are you helping me?
阿沙尼已經死了
Your handler Ashani was killed.
赫爾利去見他了 突遭意外
Hurley was with him. Something happened.
我們要去追蹤他們
I'm going after him.
我需要你的幫助
I need your help.
我們得動身了
We gotta go.
斯坦
Stan.
我等這一刻已經很久了
I've looked forward to this.
當然了 羅尼
I'm sure you have, Ronnie.
我要給你看點東西
I wanna show you something.
行啊
All right.
看看這是不是野蠻人的作為
Savages. Right, Stan?
但我不怪他們
But you know something? I don't blame them.
而怪你
I blame you.
如果你不違抗命令
Never would've happened
就不會這樣了
if you would have followed orders, Ronnie.
你陣亡了 你就成幽靈了
"You go down out there, you're a ghost."
你就消失了
"You're a John Doe."
要是你被俘了
"You get captured?"
你還記得我說的話 我真高興
Oh, you remember. That's very gratifying.
謝謝你
Thank you.
羅尼 你讓我很自豪
You made me proud today, Ron.
你應該來救我的
You should've come for me.
你將更多人置於險境
Ten men would've died.
因為你他媽的沒有遵守命令
You put 10 men's lives in danger,
你將更多人的生命置於危險之中
'cause you couldn't follow a fucking order.
- 去你媽的 - 去你媽的命令
- Fuck you. - Fuck orders.
重要的是我的性命
- Fuck the mission! - Fuck you.
我當時是你的手下 我信任你
This was me. I was your boy, I believe that.
你讓我對你深信不疑
You made me believe that.
阿沙尼讓手下
Ashani had their people tracking Minister Behruz's
追蹤比赫茲的手機位置
secure cell phone.
我們找到了比赫茲 就找到了赫爾利
So, we find Behruz, we find Hurley.
米奇
Mitch!
看看你啊
Oh, yeah, look at that.
- 你是從阿勒頗的那些人那裏學會這招的麼
Did you learn that in Aleppo?
- 不
No.
斯坦 你教過我的 要讓敵人出乎意料
You always told us what to expect, Stan.
現在告訴我你的手下在哪
Now, where's the rest of your team?
- 我的天 羅尼
Come on, Ronnie, really?
- 別再叫我羅尼了 - 你的手下在哪
Don't call me that. Where's the rest of your team?
你手下的那個新人 他一直在找我
Your new boy out there, he on my tail?
羅尼 這是你犯下的第一個錯誤
Ronnie, Ronnie, Ronnie. There's your first mistake.
審訊的時候 不要直入主題
You never start with a real question.
要循序漸進
You start slow.
進入到受審人的頭腦當中
You get inside your subject's head.
斯坦 我再問你一次
Stan, I'm gonna ask you one more time.
你犯的第二個錯誤
There's your second mistake. Number two.
第二個錯誤 就是 不要說「再問你一次」這種話
You don't say, "one more time." You already...
媽的
Damn!
斯坦 我犯的第三個錯誤是什麼
Now, what's that third mistake, Stan?
是什麼
Huh? What is it?
來啊 繼續啊
Go ahead! Go ahead!
我還有9個指甲呢 真爽
I got nine more! I like this.
真爽啊 再來啊
I like it. Go ahead, bring it on!
你個混蛋
You motherfucker!
他想知道我們外面是不是有人
Ronnie wants to know if I got a team outside.
對吧
Right, Ron?
能不能安全的將核彈運走
If it's safe to move your bomb.
是不是有人在跟蹤我們
Are we being followed?
我的這個接班人在哪
Where's the new me?
我做了調查 我瞭解他的一切情況
I've done my research. I know all about him.
你是說米奇麼
"The new me..." Oh, you mean Mitch?
我跟你說 米奇是個難以預測的傢伙
You know, Mitch, he's unpredictable.
你算不準他的
You never know about Mitch.
他行蹤不定
He might be here, he might be there.
跟你很像 但你更加瘋狂
He's like you, but you're a real Section 8.
夠了
Enough.
- 操你媽
Schizo mom.
- 他們在哪
Where are they?
- 你個沒爹養的 - 他們在哪
- Loser dad. - Where are they?
我的天
God!
你的手下在哪
Where's the rest of your team?
- 去你媽的
Half-wit mom, psycho dad...
- 你手下的其他人在哪
Where's the rest of your team?
你這人渣 - 你手下的其他人在哪
- You're pond scum. - Where are they?
你這混蛋
Pond scum! You're fucking...
關於你接頭人的事 我很難過
I'm sorry about your handler.
阿沙尼是我的叔叔
Ashani was my uncle.
肯定是比赫茲和羅斯塔米派人刺殺了他
I'm sure it was Minister Behruz
他們相對以色列發動核戰爭
and General Rostami who had him killed.
我們試圖組織他們
They want nuclear war with Israel.
在和他們的鬥爭中
We tried to stop them.
我的兄弟和父親雙雙喪命
My brother and father both died fighting them.
在這轉彎
Corviale. Turn here.
你知道我最大的錯誤
You know what my real mistake was?
就是信任你
I trusted you.
你讓我覺得我能幹出一番大事
You made me feel like I was the Second Coming.
你就像我的父親一樣
And you acted like my father.
我信賴你 信賴美利堅合眾國海軍
I trusted you and I trusted the United States Navy.
美國做的事 都是正確的 是麼 斯坦
U.S. of A. Does it, it's gotta be good. Right, Stan?
只是 從來都沒人告訴我
Except
你所負責的究竟是一個怎樣的項目
nobody told me the business y'all are really in.
你們製造出怪物
You create monsters.
這就是惡果
That's just what you do.
這麼虐待我的人
Those people who did this to me,
你覺得他們是野蠻人麼
you think they're barbarians?
扯淡
Bullshit.
我之前說的破解做的怎麼樣了
Where's the decryption I asked for?
我們開工前拉普把手機拿走了
Rapp grabbed her smartphone before we could get any of it.
目前找不到他
And we can't find him.
監控攝像頭顯示
Surveillance cameras picked up Rapp
他5分鐘前打暈了我們的一個特工
taking out our agents five minutes ago.
你這是在幹什麼呢
What the hell are you doing?
這裏發生的一切
There's not a single thing happening here
都是你一手造成的
that you didn't make happen.
上帝保佑這操蛋的美國 對吧
God bless fucking America, huh, Stan?
我不能告訴你米奇在哪
I can tell you where Mitch is...
斯坦 我犯的第三個錯誤是什麼
What's that third mistake, Stan?
- 米奇.. - 我聽不見你說的話
Mitch... I can't hear you.
我操
Fuck!
你犯的第三個錯誤 永遠不要和敵人站的太近
Third mistake, never get too close.
趕快搞定你的私事
Finish your personal business here.
你的任務已經結束了
Your work is done.
炸彈已經裝備好了
The bomb is armed.
- 啟動計時器了麼 - 是的
- Timer is set up? - Yes.
他在耍你
He's playing you.
炸彈是給他造的 不是給你的
Bomb's not for you, it's for him.
這只是他的計劃罷了
It was his plan all along!
連不上網絡
Dead zone.
這裏收不到任何信號
We're not getting any signals here.
等一下
Wait a second.
你想拿核彈幹什麼
What are you gonna do with it?
斯坦 不是我要幹什麼
No, Stan.
應該是我們要幹什麼
"What are we gonna do with it?"
羅尼 為什麼選擇羅馬這個地方啊
Why are we in Rome, Ronnie?
我喜歡羅馬
I like Rome.
這裏食物很好吃
It's good food.
永遠不要以為 我會戰死沙場
Never, ever thought I'd die in the field.
是不是覺得我很瘋狂
Ain't it crazy?
我覺得我以後想
I always figured it would be, I don't know,
住在一個森林小屋裏 帶著我的狗
some cabin in the woods with my dog.
我的話嘛
Me?
我選擇過水上生活
I think I want water.
死在海裏大概是十分平和的
There's just something peaceful about dying at sea.
來吧
All right.
結束這一切吧
Let's get it over with.
不 你想痛痛快快的死
No, you'd like that, wouldn't you?
我不會殺了你的
I ain't gonna kill you.
斯坦 我要讓你親眼見證
You're gonna live to see
你一手造成的災難
the crown of your creation, Stan.
數千美國人將會燒死
Thousands of Americans are gonna burn.
就因為你
All because of you.
好好觀賞吧
Enjoy the show.
做好準備
Get ready.
啟動倒計時
Go.
求求你救救我
Please help me.
安妮卡
Annika.
你的父母是好人
Your family were very well respected.
我是他們的朋友
They were my friends.
混蛋
Bastard.
我跟他們很熟
I knew them very well.
求求你
Please I beg you.
探測到一起爆炸
We've got an explosion detected.
在這
Here.
離菲烏米奇諾運河500米處
A half click off the Fiumicino waterways.
爆炸點位於地下
It's underground.
- 德爾塔一號小隊 開始行動 - 出發
- Delta One, go! - Let's go.
我們坐直升機過去
Get a chopper out there.
拉普 你不應該來這的
You're not supposed to be here, Rapp.
你想怎樣 把我開除?
Yeah, what are you gonna do, fire me?
那邊還有一條通道 他搞到核彈了
There's another passage down there. He's got the nuke.
- 你一個人可以吧 - 快去吧
You gonna be good?
海軍 救援直升機
Go. Go!
把槍放下
Put the gun down.
要不然她就死了
Or she's dead.
米奇 我要去見我的親人
I want to see my family, Mitch.
不 安妮卡
No, Annika, you don't.
我要去見我的親人
I want to see my family.
米奇 聽話
Come on, Mitch. Be nice.
她想活命
She wants to live.
她想去見自己的家人
She wants to see her family.
放下槍
Put the gun down.
安妮卡
Annika!
核彈會爆炸的
The bomb can't be stopped.
你什麼也做不了 就像那個在沙灘上死掉的女人一樣
Just like you couldn't stop
你救不了她
that beautiful girl from dying on the beach.
艾琳
Irene.
核彈在那艘船上
The bomb's on a boat.
赫爾利
Hurley?
你怎麼知道的
How do you know?
羅尼向在海上引爆核彈
Ronnie wanted to die at sea.
是不是第六艦隊在附近巡邏
Is the Sixth Fleet out on maneuvers?
我的天
Oh, my God.
第勒尼安海 意大利
把偵察衛星都調過來
Bring up ISR feeds.
派飛機去現場偵查情況
Get me eyes in the sky over the coastline
通知第六艦隊 發出核爆警告
and put the Sixth Fleet on nuclear alert.
湯姆
Tom.
目標是第六艦隊 他們目前離海岸線25英里
The target is the Sixth Fleet and it's 25 miles offshore.
真是太恥辱了
It's a shame.
你女朋友生前最後看到的一幕是 你沒法救她
The last thing your girl saw was you not saving her.
戰鬥警報
General quarters.
全體人員回到各自崗位
All hands, man your stations.
這不是演習 重複一遍 這不是演習
This is not a drill. I repeat, this is not a drill.
有一艘攜帶了核裝置的小艇 正在接近中
Inbound, small vessel-borne nuclear device.
Man decon stations.
小子 赫爾利是沒好好教過你麼
Didn't Hurley teach you anything, little brother?
永遠不要受制於自己的情緒
To never make it personal.
我可沒有受制於自己的情緒
This isn't personal.
糟了
Shit.
核彈上裝了計時器和起爆裝置
The bomb has a timer and a release trigger.
炸毀小船會直接引爆核彈
We take out his boat, it'll detonate.
如果核彈在水面爆炸
If it goes off above the waterline...
那會是一場災難 放射性物質會飄到大陸上空
Disaster. There'll be fallout all over the mainland.
這裏是美國海軍弗林艦 準備攻擊
USS Flynn... Prepare to engage.
小艇轉彎了
The boat is turning, sir.
誰在開船
Who's driving that boat?
那是拉普
Rapp.
去接他
Go.
- 長官您說什麼 - 去接他
- Sir? - Go!
你在幹什麼呢
What are you doing? Hurley.
赫爾利
Hurley?
我想把他救上來
Trying to get our boy to throw the bomb in the water.
弗林艦 準備好了就可以開火
Flynn, you are clear to fire when ready.
別開火 小艇已經掉頭了
Do not fire, Commander. The boat is turning.
不攻擊的話 核彈遲早會爆炸
If we don't engage, that guarantees detonation.
我知道這風險很大
I understand there's a risk,
但這是我們最好的機會了
but this is the best chance we've got.
媽的
Shit! God damn it!
他在那呢
There he is.
調至海軍無線電頻段
Get me on that boat's marine bandwidth.
拉普
Rapp!
聽到我了麼 用無線電接聽
Can you hear me? Pick up the radio!
把炸彈從船上扔下去
Throw the bomb overboard!
不行 我要帶它離艦隊遠點
No way, sir, I gotta get further away from the fleet!
拉普
Rapp!
你他媽的這輩子 就服從我的命令行不行
For once in your life, take a goddamn order!
第六艦隊要朝你開火了
The Sixth Fleet is about to blow you to hell!
指揮部 這裏是德爾塔二隊 炸彈落入水中
Command, Delta Two, the bomb's in the water.
指揮官 別開火 - 核彈落入水中
Commander, hold your fire! The bomb's in the water.
- 弗林艦 別開火
Flynn, hold fire!
別開火
Hold fire!
我們有30秒撤離
Got less than 30 seconds.
快 我們撤
All right, go! Get outta here!
我的天
Jesus.
注意 準備撞擊
Brace for impact.
是 長官
Sir, yes, sir!
我的天
Holy shit.
抓穩了
Hold on!
Brace!
你就不該來救我的
You shouldn't have come for me.
你要習慣我們經常這麼干 小子
Don't get used to it, son.
赫爾利
Hurley...
似乎我們能安全撤出去了
Looks like we're gonna be all right up here.
我是這麼覺得的
I think.
請匯報受損程度
Damage control central. Report.
壓力值正常
Pressure is normalizing.
船體多處受損
We have multiple hull breaches.
艾森豪威爾號 輻射值如何
Radiologicals, Eisenhower?
輻射值低
Low... Low levels.
啟動清潔措施
Initiating countermeasure wash-down.
- 指揮官 傷亡人數多少
Commander, any casualties?
- 弗林號受損嚴重
The Flynn took some serious damage.
尚未收到傷亡人數報告 要是炸彈沒有在水下爆炸
The casualty reports aren't in yet,
估計我們都完蛋了
but if it had gone off above the waterline, I don't think we'd be here.
艾森豪威爾號
Eisenhower,
願上帝保佑你們
my prayers are with you all.
赫爾利 拉普在麼
Hurley, is Rapp there?
等下
Hold on a minute.
是我 說吧
Yeah, go ahead.
米奇 你沒事吧
You okay, Mitch?
沒事 我挺棒的
Oh, yeah. I'm fantastic.
你今天拯救了很多人的性命
You saved a lot of lives today.
也有不少人犧牲了
Took some losses, too.
迪拜 阿聯酋
What the hell are you looking at?
你幹嘛這麼盯著我看
You look like a mummy.
你看起來像個木乃伊一樣
Yeah.
是啊
Well...
木乃伊可不用寫這些報告
A mummy doesn't have to write up reports.
你口述吧 你挺擅長做報告的
Dictate them. You should be good at that.
羅斯塔米將軍
Iranian official, General Rostami,
伊朗少數反對派領導人 在德黑蘭
the leader of the minority opposition in Tehran,
聲稱他有證據表明 美國中情局內部
claims that he has proof that a secret group
直播 爆炸性新聞 襲擊特拉維夫(以色列首都)的計劃是中情局散佈的謠言
羅斯塔米將軍宣佈競選總統
有一個秘密暗殺組織
of assassins within America's CIA
應該對上周的核爆炸事件負責
are responsible for last week's nuclear event.
伊朗總統選舉
With the Iranian presidential election
兩周後即將舉行
just two weeks away,
羅斯塔米將軍受歡迎程度正在上升
General Rostami continues to rise in popularity.
他們說羅斯塔米將軍
They say General Rostami is
是下一屆伊朗總統
gonna be the next President of Iran.
是啊
Yeah.
他現在不必把以色列炸平 就能當上總統了
He didn't even have to blow up Israel to get there.
對我們來說 他還真是個大麻煩
He's gonna be a major pain in the ass, too.
拉普在哪 我聯繫不上他
Where's Rapp? I can't reach him.
我怎麼會知道
How the hell do I know where Rapp is?
我只不過是個醫院裏的木乃伊罷了
I'm a mummy in a hospital.
羅斯塔米全力支持
Rostami has full support for restarting.
重啟伊朗核項目
Iran's nuclear program.